<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Inigo Val Slijepcevic</title>
    <link>https://inigoval.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Inigo Val Slijepcevic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://inigoval.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>about me</title>
      <link>https://inigoval.github.io/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 12:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inigoval.github.io/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Current Work I am a Machine learning/Astronomy PhD student with Prof Anna Scaife @ University of Manchester with funding from the Alan Turing Institute. I build machine learning systems that that can make reliable predictions on data gathered by telescopes from space.
Much of my work revolves around integrating uncurated image data into our models to reduce labelling cost and improve robustness to out-of-distribution data.
Previous Work &amp;amp; Education Previously, I studied Physics (4 year MPhys) at the University of Oxford, where I specialised in theoretical physics and astronomy and wrote my master&amp;rsquo;s dissertation on applying decision tree machine learning on pulsar classification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>research</title>
      <link>https://inigoval.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 12:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inigoval.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Interests I am working on building robust machine learning systems to process the vast deluge of data (exabyte scale) we are about to receive from next-generation telescopes such as the Square Kilometer Array.
Since this much data cannot be curated by humans, we need AI that can deal with messy, real-world data with few labels, unknown data sub-manifolds and out-of-distribution data.
My research has included semi-supervised learning and use of unlabelled data for improved classification in the astronomy domain, developing bespoke contrastive learning methods to apply to astronomical data-sets and use of generative algorithms to simulate astronomical objects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
